("Without intending it,
without knowing it,")
("they advance the interests of society,")
("led by an invisible hand.")
(By Adam Smith,
from "The Theory of Moral Sentiments")
When everyone acts according to
their own self-interest,
it eventually leads to balance and order.
This process is known
as the invisible hand.
To all the residents
moving into Community Town, welcome.
Community Town consists of many groups.
Groups categorized by color
will share the same living space.
Groups must trade and negotiate
with one another...
to fulfill their respective needs.
Each group has a specialized role.
Group White determines the prize money.
Group Blue manages survival.
Group Red controls the games.
Group Black distributes
food and information.
In order for all residents
to survive the full nine days...
and split the prize money,
200,000 dollars,
each group must effectively make use
of their distinct advantages.
You want us to collude?
How much should we raise the food prices?
We're not going to sell them anyway.
They're going to starve everyone all day?
Or we'll turn currency
into worthless trash.
Hyperinflation.
Fear is driving everything.
I should cause pollution.
When we have the ultimate power
over their lives,
those who are backed into a corner
will bite.
You must read trades and negotiations...
that satisfy everyone.
It's just so infuriating.
Seriously. I'm so angry.
It's going just as I planned.
Complete coexistence is impossible
with the current number.
Starve while keeping the peace.
Or start a war and shake things up.
We have no choice but to start a war.
What's the purpose?
Cut down the number of mouths to feed.
The moment a war breaks out,
there's no justice.
This is pure hypocrisy
from start to finish.
So the leader can eliminate
members of the group.
- Right.
- Yes.
Just because we had equal opportunities,
do you think our outcomes are fair?
Starting a war means...
everyone will criticize you for it.
This new world sounds amazing.
Do you want to check it out?
Before moving into Community Town,
all the residents took a test...
to assess their values and mindsets
toward financial decisions.
"A bomb threat was reported
at the Sports Complex..."
"where thousands of people are gathered."
"The only way to locate the bomb..."
"is through torturing
the terrorist's innocent child."
This is an intense question.
Is this about the trolley dilemma?
I might be able to torture the terrorist.
So it's utilitarianism versus Kantianism.
My gosh. What an awful question.
It's tiring me out.
"When a CEO earns hundreds of times
more than average workers,"
"it can hardly be justified
as fair compensation for performance."
Yes, it is fair compensation, everyone.
Work hard and become a CEO.
"The main reason the poor stay poor is
a lack of effort and will."
My gosh, this is sad.
This question is making me really sad.
Do people still say this these days?
There's an expression that goes,
"rags to riches."
Even if you're dealt the worst hand,
as long as you desperately keep trying,
you can be successful.
"In order to resolve
the national shortage of electricity,"
"a dam must be built."
(In order to resolve
the national shortage of electricity,)
(a dam must be built...)
(even over the objections
of the residents in the flooded zone.)
I can't be a politician.
Politicians are no joke.
Is the agenda of the show
making us reflect on ourselves?
My opinions are starting to change
as the questions go on.
I don't think you guys can go home today.
The Community Town Test...
measures criteria for judgment
and decisions across three levels,
and they are ethics, society,
and the individual.
The white on the left represents
an idealistic mindset,
and the black on the right represents
a pragmatic mindset.
The ethical level identifies
the decision-making criteria...
when facing moral dilemmas.
Prioritizing established principles...
over individual limitations
aligns with principlism.
Prioritizing to maximize...
the overall benefit even at the expense
of subjective decisions...
aligns with consequentialism.
"Even if an analysis
of various records and circumstances..."
"clearly predicts that
someone will commit a serious crime,"
"they cannot be detained..."
"until the actual crime..."
"has been committed." Of course, not.
What is this? A sci-fi movie?
A crime is proven through actions.
But there's something called
crime prevention.
In the US, terrorism task forces
continually investigate...
individuals with a high risk
of committing terrorism...
and try to apprehend them.
I believe that for our society
to grow in a healthy way,
doing this much is reasonable.
Come on, help us out here.
There's a 99.9 percent chance
that they will commit crimes.
"A company that violates
major public interest..."
"must be reported even if doing so
causes many innocent people..."
"to lose their jobs."
Does protecting
the major public interest...
truly outweigh the loss...
of innocent people's jobs?
I want to weigh the importance.
For example, what if
only 100 people were harmed by it?
If the numbers are about the same,
they might weigh the same.
I won't report it.
If they end up losing their jobs,
whose interest is actually being served?
But a lot of people will lose their jobs.
How can I report the company? I can't.
But the implied context
in this sentence...
is really infuriating.
I think the company should be reported.
Did I just put a bunch of people
out of work?
Yes, people will lose their jobs.
But the societal wealth
could be redirected elsewhere.
A company that violates
major public interest must be reported.
This is too hard. But I should do it.
The societal level identifies
the worldview about the distribution...
of economic resources in society.
Prioritizing institutions and policies...
to reduce inequality
is classified as structuralism.
Prioritizing individual effort
and talent...
over systemic factors
is classified as meritocracy.
"Even when hiring for organizations..."
"or corporations was purely based
on merit,"
"adjustments should be made
if diversity falls..."
"severely out of balance."
No. Merit comes first.
It's a business, after all.
What? What does this mean?
I guess it just happened naturally.
It doesn't need to be adjusted.
What I hate the most is
reverse discrimination.
I think various factors
must be taken into account.
Adjustments should be made.
That's better for companies too.
When like-minded people gather,
they only reinforce similar ideas.
Synergy is stronger
when diverse people come together.
A lot of companies have adopted
this approach these days.
Many female journalists
get hired these days.
If I'm working in HR at a company,
I'd think diversity yields better results.
According to my firsthand experience,
I'd think that this approach is
more likely to bring...
better results.
"The decline of regional cities is
a natural outcome of market dynamics."
"Therefore, spending excessive budgets
to prevent it..."
"is a waste of national resources."
No way.
Regional cities must be revitalized.
This is especially the case in Korea.
Everyone comes to Seoul.
But in the long view, regional cities
have to grow for our country to thrive.
We must spend excessive budgets on them.
There are more tasks
our government has to handle now.
Is it possible for the government
to prevent the decline of these cities?
The government grants subsidies
to farming and fishing villages.
So I read in an article that
some people did move to those villages.
But I don't think it's something
sustainable in the long run.
People love Seoul way too much.
We need a different approach.
So it might be
a waste of national resources.
The individual level identifies
an individual's life priorities.
Placing greater value
on non-monetary aspects...
is classified as leaning toward meaning.
Emphasizing that economic stability
underpins all other values...
is classified as leaning toward utility.
"Even if a politician is
somewhat corrupt,"
"I'd vote for them
as long as they grow my wealth."
Gosh,
a lot of people already vote like this.
It's like this everywhere, not just here.
People vote
in order to grow their interest.
If corruption is tolerable,
some people may vote for them.
How much are we talking?
It's not against the law.
Right. I won't be violating the law.
I'd justify my action with this excuse
and vote for them...
while I enjoy watching my wealth grow.
I can never do that.
I don't have that much money, anyway.
Grow my wealth?
I won't vote for them.
How corrupt are we talking?
I know that this politician is corrupt.
But despite that, I might vote for them.
Right?
I can't vote for them
if I know about corruption.
"When choosing a career,
personal aptitude and fulfillment..."
"must take priority
over bank account figures."
Personally speaking,
I considered my aptitude
and fulfillment in choosing my career.
Jobs are all about bank account figures.
In my opinion,
people should work for monetary gains.
Aptitude and fulfillment are for hobbies.
For example, I could get paid
100,000 dollars every day,
but I get so depressed and am miserable
whenever I have to work.
Then does the money mean anything?
The symbols representing values
across the three levels...
are divided into two.
High-density symbols indicate...
strong tendencies...
and low-density symbols indicate
weak tendencies.
When faced with limited resources
and conflicting interests,
what choices will the residents...
with different sets of values make?
Will they be able to reach negotiations...
and the perfect balance...
everyone's satisfied with?
All right then.
The game of trade and choice
will begin now.
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)
(1: What I Have and What You Want)
Hello. My name is Park Se Seung.
I actually started out
as a corporate strategy consultant.
After I starred on a dating show,
I started working full-time as a YouTuber.
Of course,
I'm going to survive until the end.
If we're playing games,
I have to win first place no matter what.
There it is.
(Community Center)
My gosh.
It looks much cooler than before.
Luna, welcome to Community Town.
Please collect your name tag
and resident notebook.
My nickname is Luna.
Moonlight is subtle, isn't it?
It softly reaches everyone.
I want to be someone
who influences others like...
how moonlight touches them.
So I picked Luna.
Luna, your color is white.
Please check your values code too.
I'd suggest...
keeping your values code a secret
from the other residents.
(Practicality: 1, Ability: 2,
Principle: 1)
(She's realistic
and values individual ability.)
When I watch competition shows...
Gosh, if I say this,
I might sound quite cruel.
Contestants
who deserve to be eliminated...
It depends on everyone's ability.
On competition shows,
it's all about the games.
Contestants who are better at these games
will survive longer.
And those contestants
should take bigger prize money.
That's the rule of these shows.
I'm quite thoughtful
and considerate of others.
But despite that, I put myself first.
I look after others
after securing my survival.
When planes are crashing,
you have to put on your oxygen mask first
before helping others.
That's how I'd describe it.
Let's say that I put on my oxygen mask.
Would I remove the oxygen mask
from the person next to me?
I hope I don't do that.
I don't think I'd do that.
Resident registration is complete.
Please go to your dormitory.
Here I go.
White...
White. Okay.
(Community Center, Staircase, White)
I made it.
(Dormitory for White)
Nice to meet you.
I'm running an organization
called Feminism with Him.
I earn my living as an educator
in sex education, gender equality,
and violence prevention.
I'm a gender equality activist.
My name is Lee Han.
When people hear that I'm an educator...
for sex education and violence prevention,
a lot of them start off
by crossing their arms.
And of course, they display hostility...
because they think I'm treating them
as potential perpetrators.
To be honest, I like that.
Let's say I go to an all-boys' high school
and the first question they ask me is,
"What do you think about prostitution?"
Then I think, "This will be a fun class"
as I walk in.
Up until a few years ago,
I wasn't aware of this problem.
When I incorporate my experience
into my lectures,
I get a lot more comments like,
"I've never heard of this before."
On this show, we're basically locked up
and forced to talk.
You guys couldn't have given me
a better environment than this.
Siseon, welcome to Community Town.
Thank you.
(He spots the resident notebook
on the table.)
(Nickname: Siseon, Group: White)
(He has a strong
and consistent idealistic tendency.)
That's easy. Good. That's a relief.
My nickname is Siseon.
I actually got the nickname
from one of my favorite novels,
"From the Gaze" by Chung Se Rang.
The female characters in the novel
are quite cool.
It's important and necessary
for me to have various perspectives.
I thought this nickname suited my career.
That's why I decided on Siseon
as my nickname.
Hello. My name is Lee Hyun Seon.
I work for Explosive Ordnance Disposal
at Korea Airports Corporation.
Ever since I was in fourth grade,
I just wanted to join the military.
When I was in the special forces,
I served as a demolition specialist.
After getting discharged,
I wanted to continue the career path
I began in the military.
So I decided to apply for KAC.
(Nickname: Boss, Group: White)
I wanted to go with Big Boss like
the character Song Joong Ki played...
in "Descendants of the Sun."
I asked my family
what they thought of my nickname.
They said "big" didn't suit me.
So I just went with Boss.
"Meaning, Ability, and Principle."
(She's an idealist
but values individual ability.)
I value...
people and honor over money.
It made me want to survive on this show...
without abandoning my values.
My name is KNUCKS.
I'm a professional dancer.
Every competition show I've been on
has always been an absolute battlefield.
As for "Bloody Game,"
it was a pretty intense game.
"Street Man Fighter" was also intense.
When I watched the first season
of The Community,
the show was quite thought-provoking.
I may not look like the type,
but I'm quite gentle.
I thought I would learn a lot
from this show.
So I'm looking forward to my time here.
Goodness.
Paul, welcome to Community Town.
Please collect your name tag
and resident notebook.
My gosh.
This is pretty cool.
(Nickname: Paul, Group: White)
"Paul" is actually a religious name.
Here's how I'd describe him.
Through an unexpected event,
he broke out of his existing views...
and spared his faith.
To be honest, if there are things
I need to change about myself,
I'm ready to change them
to turn the tables around on this show.
So I went with Paul.
"Ability, one."
(Meaning: 2, Ability: 1, Principle: 2)
This isn't my ability level.
(He's a strict idealist
who values individual ability.)
(The veteran contestant
looks around the center.)
I see something here.
Okay.
Something's here.
It's cool.
My name is Shin Hye Won.
I've been a journalist for 14 years.
I mostly covered
social issues and politics.
Back when I was
covering the National Assembly,
I alternated between...
covering the ruling and opposition parties
for a long time.
I meet real-life politicians who operate
in the world of actual politics.
Despite the political figures...
participating in the first season,
it was very much idealistic
compared to actual politics.
In the first season,
individual judgment regarding values
was the key element.
But these elected politicians...
don't act purely out of their values.
I believe that it happens quite often
that they champion certain values...
only for those values
to turn out to be self-serving.
Yes. I have to be careful.
(Nickname: Leia, Group: White)
(Leia)
(Meaning: 2, Structure: 1, Principle: 2)
(Her tendency is consistently idealistic.)
I gave myself a nickname
after a character in "Star Wars."
She's a princess,
but doesn't shy away from the conflicts.
She takes charge at the forefront.
After watching this side of her character
in the movie,
I picked her name to be my nickname.
I have a unique job.
I'm a board game developer.
My name is Kim Geon Hee.
You know games
like Halli Galli, Zenga, and Rummikub?
Every board game
has a developer behind it.
It's like how books have authors.
Board game developers come up with rules.
People follow the rules
while playing the games,
and they have fun.
My job is to design
that kind of fun through games.
"Resident notebook of Community Town."
"Hamlet."
(Nickname: Hamlet, Group: White)
My nickname is Hamlet.
I actually think
Hamlet is a strong character.
When you read "Hamlet,"
it seems everyone has a plan.
Some plot revenge and so on.
They try to be smart and make plans.
But they all end up dead.
It's all about his survival.
He has to consider death.
Just like him, I'll put my life
on the line and try my best to survive.
(Meaning: 2, Structure: 2, Principle: 2)
(Hamlet is a strict idealist.)
I was surprised.
"Was I this transparent?"
Here's an example.
It was easy for me to decide...
when I was forced to violate existing laws
to do something.
A lot of people must have spent years...
deliberating to craft these laws.
But should I violate these laws
to pursue what I believe is justice?
I shouldn't do that.
I clearly knew where I stood there.
"Resident notebook of Community Town."
"Resource storage."
- Hello.
- My gosh, hello.
I should have opened the door for you.
Boss? Our boss is here.
- Everyone is in White?
- Yes, we're all in White.
I think this is the dormitory for White.
The bathroom.
You have to push it
if you want to open it.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
This can't be everyone.
- This is just for White.
- This is for Group White.
- I guess this is a team match.
- Yes.
You must've been flustered
since you were the first one in.
- There are three rooms.
- Twenty people...
- That's...
- All the rooms look great.
- So 3 of us might have to share it.
- There are only 3 rooms.
The three of us might end up
sharing the room together.
That's possible.
I think the staff picked
only good-looking people.
Everyone here is so young.
Having a chance to communicate
with young people is quite rare...
- these days.
- So you don't consider yourself young?
I wouldn't say I'm young.
- I'm not young.
- Gosh, you are young.
No.
I watched the first season.
- It's very different.
- Yes.
- This is a completely different concept.
- But...
- No one can see this, right?
- Right.
If you think about it, we'll be roommates.
Trying to figure out
each other's values code at night...
might be a bit hard.
In the last season of The Community,
the test ranked the residents...
across 4 levels with 3 sub-tiers each.
(Ideology Verification Open)
There was a rule...
where guessing another resident's score
by using this information...
would get them eliminated.
Attacking another resident
with Ideology Verification was possible.
(Ideology Verification Attack
utilized the scores.)
So the code has three letters.
And the number represents...
the level of intensity, right?
- One must be moderate. Two, intense.
- Two.
- That must be it.
- That's it.
Then isn't it much easier
to figure out the code?
- It's much easier compared to before.
- Yes.
There are fewer combinations now.
As long as we don't attack each other...
- I'm in big trouble.
- You know what I just thought of?
I'm getting a feeling that
most of us might be leaning toward White.
What?
- That crossed my mind.
- You gave us a hint.
- But...
- Well...
What you just said
could have caused a lot of trouble.
- He gave us a hint.
- That's how much I trust you guys.
- Already?
- Right?
- Yes. I don't want to fight either.
- Yes.
- I already like you guys.
- That was sudden.
- One of us could be leaning toward Black.
- That's possible.
It's possible that someone has all Blacks.
- Let's be careful.
- Be careful.
I'll do my best.
- I get why we ended up in Group White.
- Why?
Everyone looks so innocent,
like the color white.
All of you.
I guess it's Black and White.
- That might be the theme, right?
- Right?
- We're Red.
- Yes.
I think we're split
into color-coded teams.
- Do you think we're in here together...
- Right. We...
because we have things in common?
- Well, should we...
- You like red.
open up about our political leanings?
- Why red?
- Right.
Hello.
I'm participating as Donkey.
I'm a stand-up comedian, Park Cheol Hyeon.
I chose Donkey as my nickname...
because I actually like donkeys.
Horses jump off a cliff
when their owners tell them to jump.
But donkeys go,
"What? If I jump, I'll die."
They can be stubborn like that.
Let's say...
Do you call them reins? Or a leash?
Anyway, even if someone's holding them,
I want to be someone...
who's stubborn enough
to make his own decisions and speak up.
So I chose Donkey.
(He values meaning over money.)
(But he's a strict realist.)
I remember a lot of questions
similar to the trolley dilemma.
My thoughts depended on the day.
On days I was stressed,
I felt like wishing a lot of them dead.
You know what it's like.
Even if I act in good conscience,
there are instances
where many of those involved get hurt.
When I feel like problems...
are beyond my control,
I tend to pull back from them.
I'm Donkey.
- Donkey?
- Yes.
You can call me Izaha.
- Izaha?
- Yes.
- I have a four-syllable name.
- Right.
- Maillard.
- You can call me however you want.
I'm guessing
you're pretty good at cooking.
I swear...
- I've seen you around.
- Right.
I don't know who you are exactly,
- but you seem like a good cook.
- Right.
My name is Mok Jin Hwa.
I go by the handle "Seungwoos Dad,"
and I post cooking videos.
My nickname is Maillard,
which comes from what made me famous...
in my videos.
The Maillard reaction...
refers to the browning process
that happens...
when meat is cooked at high heat.
A lot of the questions...
were about
whether I'd sacrifice the minority...
for the greater good.
I'd willingly sacrifice myself instead.
I play online games,
and moments come up...
where I have to choose
between killing 1 person or saving 5.
I made that choice recently...
to achieve our shared goal.
Anyway, I'm a "T."
I find it difficult to understand people
who always react...
emotionally first.
Sleeping well...
Wait, what are those numbers?
Is that a puzzle we need to solve?
That's 352461...
Don't you think there's something to it?
There's a reason
they put books around here.
(They take a strategic approach
from the very start.)
The subtitle for the show
is "Invisible Hand."
- I see.
- That's right.
It's the metaphor Adam Smith used
to illustrate free market principles.
The economy must be the theme this time.
This is about currency.
It keeps going on about the trust
in the system.
Maybe it's a contest to see
who can earn trust.
Trust, the system...
I have a feeling
we'll be dabbling in that.
Hi, I'm Lee Jae Yong.
As an accountant,
I consult for small companies,
make investments, give lectures,
and make broadcast appearances,
among other things.
In our field, accountants...
are known as the watchdogs of capitalism.
We analyze the situation
and offer advice...
based on data...
so others can make informed decisions.
(Izaha)
I go by Izaha,
named after the main character
in one of my favorite web novels,
"Return of the Mad Demon."
His nickname is actually Mad Demon,
just like the title suggests,
and his mood swings
are totally unpredictable.
He can be ruthless one moment...
and merciful the next,
but he's genuinely considerate at heart.
Deep down, he has a strong desire...
to protect the vulnerable and the weak.
I wanted to come across as fun,
slightly unhinged, yet warmhearted,
so that's why I chose that nickname.
(Meaning 2, Structure 2, Principle 1)
I feel a lot more at ease
knowing that we're a team.
Here's one thing I was concerned about
before coming here.
I was facing a real dilemma,
knowing I'd be branded an enemy
the moment I even considered...
- taking someone out.
- That's right.
Realizing we're a team
made me see that we'll have...
- to pull together to survive.
- Exactly.
The moment you start plotting,
you put a target on your back.
I think that's why we were put...
- in separate rooms.
- I agree.
What happens...
if we get a clean shot...
- at taking out the other teams?
- Right.
Would you take them out
without hesitation?
In that case,
I'm not planning on making nice...
with the opposing teams.
Of course.
What do you think was the reason behind
giving us blue?
I'm drawing a blank.
Are we competing as teams? No, right?
- Is it a team game?
- Probably not, right?
You look awfully familiar.
- Really?
- Yes.
You might've seen me before.
I could be mistaken, but...
That could be the case.
My name is Lee Soo Min,
and I'm an actress.
I was in that show so long ago
that it's embarrassing to say now.
But yes, I'm the girl from "Boni Hani."
"Boyfriend on Demand" was
a huge hit recently,
so I've been getting recognized
for that instead lately.
It brings a smile to my face.
My nickname, Pitou?
I rescued a cat once,
and I happened to be rewatching
the anime "Hunter X Hunter..."
at the time.
In the show,
there's a cat-like character
named Neferpitou.
I considered naming my cat Pitou,
but I went with Bbangyi instead.
Still, the name felt too good to pass up,
so I'm using it as my nickname here.
I've always thought of myself...
as someone
who stands firm in their beliefs.
But watching this show made me realize...
that I'm easily swayed.
Every time someone brought up
a different point,
I agreed with them,
and then I turned right around...
and agreed with the next person.
Honestly, I was like that the whole time.
Since I can't claim to be the smartest...
or most knowledgeable person here,
I'll stick to something more realistic.
Something like loyalty.
I'm not sure
how much I can share about myself.
Exactly. How much are we allowed to...
Is our age a secret as well?
Then again,
I'm at a point in my life
where I'd rather not reveal my age.
Really?
I mean, I'm happier
to keep the number hidden.
My name is Im Ji Eun,
and I'm a writer...
specializing mostly in essays.
People first learned about me...
through my debut essay collection
on feminism.
I guess my perspective
is rooted a lot in classism.
Classism sounds like a heavy word,
and the concept feels kind of abstract.
Back in season one,
we were asked
if we'd ever seen a rat in our house.
I actually have.
I feel like even the idea of self-esteem
is rooted in class background.
There are people...
who grew up with a life...
where they could afford to make mistakes.
Meanwhile, there are those
whose single mistake...
would mean serious consequences.
Their attitudes toward life
couldn't be more different,
and even that's tied to class as well.
My nickname is Salt.
I'm all about that frugal life.
I'll show you what kind of survivor I am.
(A consistent and strict idealist)
People from various fields
were featured...
on the first season.
For me, Genie...
I mean,
the Peking duck...
(Genie's speech mission in season 1)
I absolutely love Peking duck,
but I felt so hurt and miserable...
that I bawled,
crying that I wanted Peking duck.
(The Peking duck story that turned heads)
We couldn't be more different,
and her story rubbed me the wrong way.
Framing her Peking duck story...
as the most painful moment of her life?
That just made me roll my eyes.
And there was that time...
when an immunity pass
was completely useless.
She dragged it out
until the very last moment...
and had to make a run for it.
(Genie had the power
to save someone from elimination.)
(She dragged it out
until the very last moment.)
(She ended up failing to make the save.)
Who heads out running
with only ten seconds left?
She was just covering her bases.
It was obvious
she wouldn't make it in time.
(A lot of people called Genie out
for her actions.)
In more ways than one,
she got on my nerves.
Frankly, it was hard not to view her...
as selfish.
Hi, I'm back home.
I'm Genie.
I used to have an office job back then,
but now I'm a freelancer
working in broadcasting...
as an actor and entertainer.
Following that show, I was cast...
in two other survival shows,
which got me labeled as someone
obsessed with the genre.
Being able to challenge myself
to do all kinds of things...
is a huge advantage.
I got mocked endlessly
over that Peking duck story.
Still, people around me
started buying me Peking duck,
which I happily devoured.
My speech from that day
keeps showing up...
in short clips online,
and judging by the comments,
people really despised me for it.
People have been targeting me
because of that.
(Practicality 2, Ability 2, Principle 1)
What do they mean?
Practicality, ability, principle?
(Extremely money-driven, standing
as the only Level 2 practical player.)
"Ability."
Can I keep this pen?
No one's answering? I'm taking it then.
(Genie, TV entertainer)
I'm going to show them
how having prior experience...
gives you an edge.
I've got to defend the pride
of season one.
"Don't even think you're on my level."
Just let me naturally lead you,
and you follow.
You'll be in good hands.
That's all I want to say.
"Rather not be noticed..."
Wait, is this the place?
- No way.
- Is someone else joining us?
- Well...
- Why don't I get the door?
- Coming.
- No way.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hello.
- Wait, aren't you...
- Hello.
- Right?
- That's right.
(They immediately recognize Genie.)
Yes, it's me. You probably watched...
- season one before coming here.
- Right.
- I mean...
- I wonder why the three of us...
are a team.
This place is so pretty.
We took the time to briefly...
introduce ourselves,
but you don't really need to.
I know, she's...
Her entrance is
all the introduction she needs.
How can you do this to me?
I didn't hold back at all...
about how much I hated...
(Salt, Author)
Genie.
How can you do something so evil...
as putting me in the same room as her?
When she walked through the door...
I took vegetable melatonin yesterday,
which can cause nightmares
as a side effect.
Could what I'm experiencing...
be a nightmare caused by it?
What was she doing here?
She was actually here, and both of them...
were wearing tweed jackets...
as if they were mocking me.
Talk about death by fashion.
I mean,
my nickname is Salt,
but I didn't want to come across as cheap.
I was completely thrown off.
I stayed up late...
watching season one
of The Community last night.
What?
It didn't seem real.
I felt like I was dreaming.
Judging by what I saw on season one,
I didn't think we'd get along.
She always seemed to choose
the opposite of what I chose,
so I worried about how we'd get along.
I wonder what this is.
A stamp?
Is this for when we vote?
- Experience working at its best.
This is exactly why
having experience is valued.
- Tell me about it.
- No way.
It feels embarrassing to be praised
for something like this.
I didn't know the two.
But they seemed to be nice people
from the start.
They're good to be with as they're nice,
but I was quite worried about...
whether these herbivores would be okay.
You must be quiet in general, Paul.
Sorry? No.
- No?
- No.
Paul doesn't seem to be one of us.
- That could be the case.
- No.
- In my opinion,
- He's being too strategic.
he's like that on the outside,
but he's full of air inside.
Right.
- I'm an airhead.
- He's full of air.
I strongly thought that these people
hadn't been on a survival show before.
"This is the calm before the storm."
It felt like they were trying to
make me the villain.
They were all bubbly,
and it was hard to bear that.
"Will I be able to compete
in a team game with these people?"
It was my first time feeling
so drained in a survival show.
It was so tough.
I'm...
- Gosh!
Something's playing.
All residents have moved in.
In the resource storage
within the dormitory you have moved into,
there are three types of resources
that will be used here.
From now on,
I will explain the three types
of resources in Community Town.
They are diamonds, lives, and credits.
I'll start with the diamonds.
Diamonds are equivalent
to the prize money of the residents.
- Diamonds.
- Right.
The total prize money
of 200,000 dollars...
will be based on...
the number of diamonds acquired
at the end of the residency.
Each resident will earn the prize money
based on the number of diamonds acquired.
- They're like chips.
- There are currently 200 diamonds.
- Thus, 1 diamond is worth 1,000 dollars.
- It's 1,000 dollars.
Next are the lives.
Life represents the lives
of the residents.
At the time when all official activities
come to an end,
each of you must submit one life.
When a resident fails to submit
a life at that moment,
that resident will be removed immediately.
When removed,
the acquired diamonds may not be
earned as prize money.
However, when there is one resident left
in a group,
that resident will not be removed
even with zero lives.
Oh, I see!
Next are the credits.
Credits represent the opportunities
of the residents.
All activities in Community Town...
require credits.
More credits will provide...
more choices for the residents.
For the residents to collect the diamonds
as prize money,
lives must be collected to be able
to survive until the end.
In this whole process,
credits will be needed.
I wish all of you the best of luck.
For more details,
open the rule card envelope
placed on the table.
- Can we open this now?
- Yes.
We can open the envelope, right?
- I'll open it.
- Right.
We have 200 diamonds,
- eight lives,
- Eight lives,
- and 3 credits.
If there are 8 lives
when there are 6 of us,
we'll be left with 2 if we use 1 each.
Right. That's how it will be.
I'm sure we'll have to use our diamonds
to buy lives in the future.
I believe so.
That will bring down the prize money.
There are eight lives?
But there are six of us.
Does that mean we're safe
only for a single day?
One must...
be given a couple of days to live...
to be able to think about something else.
We might end up dying the next day.
I thought that I had to start moving
right away...
to get more lives.
Life stood out to me the most.
For us to survive another day,
we had to secure four more.
I thought about how we could
secure more lives.
- All of our numbers are here.
- Right.
- Lives are the most important.
- We can live for a day.
- Right.
- One day.
- Two must be removed the next day.
We have to earn two more today...
- for all of us to survive the next day.
- Or...
What if there are 2 lives left
when there are 3 of us?
- Right.
- Who must leave?
Must the three of us fight each other?
- That's how it's structured.
- Right.
- It's because...
we need 3 lives each day
for the 3 of us to survive.
If we are to survive as a team,
we are to know that
it's going to be tough.
We must know what we can do
with the cards.
- Thirty?
- Thirty lives right now?
We have zero diamonds.
Should we open it?
Was that the end of the explanation?
(They will have 6 lives left
after surviving until the end.)
The 200,000 dollars...
That was exactly what was said.
More credits will provide
more choices for the residents.
- That's it.
- Okay.
It's a summary...
- what was said.
- It's just like the announcement.
The voting paper is here.
- Voting paper?
- It's just for us.
Will we pick a leader?
- It's voting paper.
- Right.
We must submit it.
- Earlier,
- Right.
we were told that the last one left...
will not get removed
even with no lives left.
Must the three of us
compete against each other?
What?
It says...
that's only for that last one left.
If one of us survives...
The leader will be chosen now.
- You will be given 30 minutes...
- Leader?
to discuss freely...
and choose a leader.
- Within our team?
- Within our team.
Once a resident becomes a leader,
the leader will continue
to be the leader...
unless a revote is decided.
The revote for a leader...
can be called out every morning.
Every morning?
- There are just three of us.
- We must choose a leader.
- Right.
We have 30 minutes left.
Is there anyone who wishes
to be the leader?
Anyone who wishes to be the leader?
Well, I tend to be the leader often.
I want to become the leader as well.
- Great.
- Really?
Great.
What about you, Boss?
I don't have a strong desire
to become one,
- but I will accept that role.
- You will accept that role?
- I thought she really wanted the role.
- Me?
- Because I'm Boss?
- Right.
- Because she's Boss?
- Her name says she's a leader?
- Right.
- Because of the name "Boss?"
- We must have a specific goal set...
- Right.
for us to decide.
Simply put,
it could be, "Let's make a lot of money."
Or it could be,
"Let's collect a lot of lives..."
"and stay alive for a long time."
Personally, I think lives...
should be the first priority.
The second priority should be credits,
and the third priority
should be prize money.
It's the same for me.
Right. I was going to say that.
We can decide if we want to
go for more prize money...
even if it requires sacrificing our lives.
This is what I mean by saying that.
I obviously want everyone to survive,
but to me,
my life is more precious
than the prize money.
- Your life?
- Right.
- I want to survive.
- I see.
When we decide on a leader,
I want the leader to protect my life
more than my money.
Right.
A leader must be...
quite ambitious...
to be able to keep us alive.
- Right.
- I wish it to be someone...
who is talented in that area.
Instead of me being the leader,
I think Luna, who is more calculative...
- "Calculative?"
- Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
- I meant you were...
- When did I form that image?
I'm not someone
who is competition-oriented.
That was why I recommended Luna
to become our leader.
Thank you.
If I am to recommend myself,
I have a lot of experience...
with being a leader.
I tend to volunteer to be the leader...
in gatherings.
I'm quite competitive as well.
Right.
When there are other teams,
I tend to try my best...
- to protect my team.
- Great.
We chose Luna.
It was by unanimous consent.
In a community,
there are leaders and followers.
I believe the followers
must fully respect the leader's opinion.
Luna expressed herself well,
so I believed she deserved that role.
I want to become the leader, though.
I will take that role if I get the chance.
At a certain moment,
I will ask for a revote.
"Others must also be given a chance."
"I want to be given that chance."
I'm ready to make that claim.
I thought about wanting to become
the leader even when I was at home.
Once I become the leader,
I will be given more information.
I did volunteer to become the leader,
thinking that I might be given
at least one more life.
I thought it was a role
that I had to take.
(Luna, Team White leader)
Seeing you, Luna,
I was reminded of Genie
out of the Season One characters.
- Right.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I'm not that type.
Genie went over the line.
- She went over the line?
- Right.
If the leader...
doesn't have to be the leader...
until the very end,
how about we each take turns?
We have a lot of time anyway.
- Sounds good.
- Right.
Do any of you want to go first?
No.
The one with experience should go first.
The one with experience.
- That will make me feel comfortable.
- If you're okay with that.
This is a completely new game,
- so it won't mean much.
- Right.
If you feel comfortable with that,
I'll give it a try.
- You two can each take turns.
- Right.
- Right. Sounds good.
- Okay.
Being the leader...
out of three kids?
It didn't feel that significant.
Being the leader of three
didn't seem like a big advantage.
But they wanted me
to be the leader for the first day.
I would also ask the one
from the previous season to go.
I just went, "All right, then."
The number three,
based on my girls' middle school
and high school days,
was a number that always caused disorder.
If the other two team up
and vote against me,
I'll get kicked out right away.
There seems to be a system of...
"It's every man for himself."
When there is one survivor in the team,
lives become useless.
I get those thoughts...
from the number three.
I think I'm in the middle.
The two seem to be...
quite distant from each other.
Ultimately, it'll be easier
for the only one left in the group,
as lives won't be needed at all.
If this wasn't a team game...
and it was a battle between
the three of us,
I would feel really scared.
I had to see what rights
and privileges the leader was given.
That was why I asked us
to each take turns.
Who will become the leader?
What rights will the leader be given?
How will those resources be distributed?
I'm fine with letting someone else
become the leader,
but whoever the leader is,
I wish for our team to focus
on collecting more lives.
Right. We must focus on that.
- I just wish the leader won't want to...
- Yes.
survive on his own and let the others die.
- Becoming the leader of us...
- Right.
- should mean we're all on the same side.
I believe our team is quite competitive
when it comes to brain power.
- I don't see ourselves leaving early.
- Right.
- We have a good chance.
Until the end,
- we should try to survive...
- Right.
- to the best of our abilities.
- I agree.
- Right.
So our leader is Maillard?
It should be Maillard.
He's someone
who has a bit of fighting spirit.
I like that beard.
The beard? It's the beard of a leader.
- Right.
- He has the face of a leader.
Wherever he goes,
- he won't give in.
- He won't give in.
- So Maillard will be our leader.
- I agree.
- I'll try being a leader for a day.
- Right.
- We'll see how it goes.
- So that's decided.
- Right.
It got decided all of a sudden.
My teammates said it was
because of my beard.
My teammates all pretend to be humble,
but they are people
who can take this role.
We're all the same.
It seems like we're all
trying to read the room.
The leader selection is over.
Please head to the Community Center...
to register the leader of your group.
It's Genie.
Genie, congratulations
on becoming the leader.
Pick up the resource storage key...
and put on the leader badge.
This must be used
for the thing in our room.
- The resource storage.
- Right.
I understand why people feel proud
of becoming a leader of any minor group.
Putting on a badge...
made me feel somewhat proud.
This is what it feels like right now.
When I was in elementary school,
I dreamt of these moments
while taking a nap after piano class.
- What kind of dream is that?
- Why is it so specific?
- What?
What was that?
You have N in your MBTI, don't you?
Yes.
A total intuitive.
- A total intuitive.
- Right.
This must be it. It looks pretty.
We must be the first group here.
Really?
(Town Hall)
- Gosh, the menu brings back memories.
- Gosh!
"Supermarket Rules."
"Products must be purchased with
the number of diamonds Black asks for."
- Black?
- Who is Black?
- Is someone here?
- I guess so.
Gosh, they look good.
I'm hungry.
- Should we sit?
- They should be coming.
Let's take the best seats.
This place looks really nice.
I wonder why we were chosen to be
Team Blue.
I don't think we were put together
based on our teamwork.
I thought you were an intuitive.
Just now...
- That hurt me a bit.
- Just now...
- I didn't mean it like that.
- What you just said sounded like,
"I don't think I'll get along with you."
- Gosh.
- No.
- "It's every man for himself."
- After having a conversation,
we all felt different.
You felt that right away?
- There are people inside.
- Right.
Hey!
- Hello.
- Shall we sit first?
- Right.
- Take a seat.
- Thank you.
We are Team Red.
- Right.
- We are Team Blue.
You're the leader.
- Could we see your nicknames?
- Right.
- I'm Salt.
- Salt.
Three men came in.
The one in front had a beard!
I felt afraid. I felt overwhelmed.
They looked like mathematicians.
The three of us looked like kids,
and they felt like game freaks.
If there's a deathmatch between our teams,
we are going to get destroyed.
That was the first thought I got.
Team Red was in my prediction.
I kept seeing...
a mix of white, blue, and red inside.
I expected to be 3 teams of 3.
That was my prediction,
and a group of three came in.
I was sitting there thinking,
"As expected."
But Black came in on his own
out of nowhere.
"I didn't expect this at all."
- Hello.
- Black?
- He's Black.
He's Black?
- The owner of the supermarket?
- The owner of the supermarket.
Right. I'm the merchant.
- I see!
- Hello.
- Gosh!
Hello. I'm a businessman
and TV personality.
My name is Jung Jae Ho.
My nickname is Vector.
Vector means speed.
As there's a certain direction,
there's a vector value.
To represent me as someone
charging endlessly toward a goal,
I decided to go with the name "Vector."
Your color is black.
As black is a group of one,
you naturally become the leader.
Team Black will become the merchant
of Community Town.
Merchant?
The merchant decides the prices
of the items in the supermarket.
The prize money is earned
by selling those items.
The first time I was on TV...
was through a show called "Heart Signal."
I was also in a show called
"The Black Sheep Game."
Recently, I was in "Synchro Game."
I became the winner
after winning all four rounds.
I believe my decision-making
is faster than others.
I believe I can move quickly...
after making wise decisions.
Are you alone in your team?
So you're the leader.
- Right. I have the leader badge.
- He's alone.
You're alone?
I'm alone.
Do you use a room alone?
- Yes.
- That's so nice.
- Do you all share the same room?
- Hold on!
- You spoke your heart right away.
- We were all thinking that inside.
- Right.
- Really?
- How did he earn this privilege?
Exactly.
(He listened to the announcement
on his own.)
Hold on.
That was why there were no prices
at the supermarket.
I can come up with the prices.
Could there be another role
other than the merchant?
That was the saddest part.
I love using the room on my own,
but others can chat all they want,
and they have someone to talk to
when feeling bored.
I was left alone in the room...
talking to myself
even during the leader selection.
Everything else is great,
but those parts make it hard for me.
I want to be on Team Black.
I don't know why I was given this role.
- You can make a lot of money.
- Right.
Right. I believe so.
- You all must make purchases to survive.
- Then,
the conditions must be different for him.
Have you been told the details?
I sell items to make money.
What?
Is this Nexus: The Kingdom of the Winds?
- Nexus: The Kingdom of the Winds?
- Well...
I know nothing. I think I'll go...
and check the things I can sell.
- Right.
- Please give me a moment.
This person will sell things
at the supermarket...
and earn diamonds? No.
This person knows a lot.
That is why I must get close to him.
He seems to know a lot.
First of all, he was really good-looking.
He didn't seem like someone
who would play tricks.
He had an image of an upright young man.
Vector was someone...
I met a few times in League of Legends.
We just knew each other's names.
But even that made me feel so relieved.
I had one person I knew.
Would you all like a cup of coffee?
- Are you giving these to us for free?
- Yes.
- Yes!
- Really?
Well, I'm the merchant.
I can do whatever I want.
- I'll take the loss.
- I see.
You all look tired.
I know what this is.
- Right.
- Would you like a latte?
- He's making us get addicted.
- Right.
What would you like?
- Can we really have these?
- Right.
- We won't get sick, will we?
- No.
We won't be charged later, will we?
She already drank it.
- Right.
- She already drank it.
You won't be charging us, right?
We have no money.
What?
- What?
- Hello.
- Why are there so many people?
- What?
- There are more people there.
- There are so many of them.
There are so many of them.
- Hello.
(All the residents finally meet
for the first time.)
There are seven.
- Hello.
They are in odd numbers.
Right.
A large group of six for Team White
came over all of a sudden.
I felt intimidated for a moment.
The female members
also felt quite powerful.
A legion came over.
That felt really intimidating.
Numbers meant a lot.
They went,
"Why are there so many of them?"
That is actually our weakness.
That means we have to spend more
of our resources.
There were six of us.
There's a sense of mediocrity
that can be felt...
from a large number.
"Are we the leftovers?"
I felt slightly annoyed
while thinking that.
Genie.
Why is she here?
Why has she come again?
The one in Team Red
was someone in the accounting field.
I thought that things would feel
much different for them.
There were many mouths to feed.
But the many members
could be used to their advantage.
They all gave off good first impressions.
The members of Team Red
had the worst first impressions.
For some reason,
it feels like you were friends like this,
- and you were friends like this.
- Based on their images.
- Did the members of Team White...
- They all look like...
all know each other?
No. It's our first time seeing each other.
It feels like
an intimidatingly large family.
- Right.
- It feels like we're short on numbers.
They all look close.
But if you all think about it,
season one was about
ideology verification.
- Right.
- We all know Genie's ideology.
- So, that's not our goal for this season.
- Right.
If so, I have to leave today.
- It's not verification.
I think it would be great to...
- think about the purpose of this season.
- Right.
Residents who have moved into
Community Town,
welcome.
I will explain the rules...
for your 9 days and 8 nights
of stay in Community Town.
Community Town consists of several groups.
The members of each group
of different colors live together.
The dorm of another group
can not be entered.
All information,
including resource status,
may not be shared...
and must be kept confidential
from each group.
The schedule of 9 days and 8 nights
will operate like this.
Productive activities will take place
in the morning.
Trade activities will take place
in the afternoon.
Every dinner must be eaten...
with all groups gathered in the Town Hall.
- All groups gathered?
- There's a time for trading.
Each group has a specialized skill.
Team White can decide the prize money.
The diamonds that are used as a standard
of prize money distribution...
can only be issued by Team White.
After trading with Team White,
secure your prize money.
Gosh, that's really important.
- That's why the colors are like that.
- Right.
- Team Blue decides survival.
- That was what the colors meant.
The absolute majority of lives required
for survival...
can be produced by Team Blue.
In order to avoid elimination...
- and survive until the end,
- Let's go!
- make good deals with Team Blue.
- Good.
- That's great.
That's important.
Team Red controls the game.
Credits are required for all activities.
Team Red has an overwhelming efficiency
when it comes to credit production.
Without Team Red's credits,
all activities will stop.
That must stop
all profit-making activities.
Only Team Black...
will be able to check
the resource information.
Use Team Black
to check each other's information.
However, Team Black is not required
to share the information accurately.
Throughout the whole 9 days and 8 nights,
all groceries may only be purchased
at Team Black's supermarket.
That must be so exciting.
To run the supermarket,
one life is required for one day.
As today is the first day,
the supermarket can be used
without a life.
- That's a relief.
- That would've been terrible.
So each group will produce
their respective resources in the morning.
- Right.
- All of us must work hard...
for us to prosper.
I believe so.
I thought it was well-balanced.
All three resources were connected,
and not even one of them
could be left out.
All three resources were necessary.
All of them played a part.
The dominant strategy of this situation...
is to persuade the others that
our resource is the most valuable.
Economically, it's the Invisible Hand.
The Invisible Hand...
represents everyone's greed
gathered together,
forming reasonable market prices.
A beneficial result for everyone...
is the outcome of this.
The current total amount of resources
of Community Town will be revealed.
After this announcement,
there will be no more announcements.
(Total Resources)
So there's a total of 43 lives.
- What? That's not right.
- We have 43?
- That's the total number.
Don't they have all of them?
(Team Blue Lives: 30)
- But...
- In our room,
there was a display of our lives...
- and our credits.
- Those are excluded?
Each group has its
own number of resources.
All groups must reveal their numbers...
- for us to know.
- Right.
- But they can't be revealed.
- Aren't we supposed not to?
- That will put you at a disadvantage.
- Right.
Good deals must be made with each other.
This is a funny situation.
That's including Team Black, right?
Yes. I believe that includes my resources.
(Team Black's Resources:
0 diamonds, 1 life, 0 credits)
I only had one life.
I was already the only one left
in my team,
so lives were meaningless to me
when it comes to survival.
Does that mean the lives are only useful
for me to open the store?
I opened the rule book,
and it said that Team Black could not
make deals regarding lives or credits.
"Will I have to close down
after opening the store tomorrow?"
I was filled with all kinds of thoughts.
I didn't think the resources
would be this imbalanced.
We had 30 of 36 credits.
Since Team Black cannot make deals
with credits,
if I infer that the other teams
were given three,
that's ten times more for our team.
That made me think that
we could take a dominant position.
Each team was stacked
with their respective resource.
The members of Team White
were short on lives.
They must be the ones
who feel the most anxious.
Team Red had enough
to survive for two days,
but it seemed like we had
the most power at this point.
But the other teams were given...
small amounts of credits and lives.
Why didn't we get a small amount
of diamonds?
We should've been given diamonds.
The trading for Day 1 will begin.
Each group may freely
negotiate for three hours.
When a deal is made,
the leaders of the groups...
must bring the resources from the dorms...
and visit the Community Center
with their trade partners.
(Occupied: Please wait.)
Two groups can make a trade at once.
When one credit
is put into the credit box,
the Trading Station will be activated.
When the resources are inserted
into the Trading Station,
the deal begins.
Black is the operator of the supermarket.
Please enter the supermarket
and start your business.
While wishing everyone good deals,
this announcement
at the Community Center will now end.
- I see.
- Right.
The theme is Invisible Hand.
The trade system
is at the center of everything.
We must understand which resource
has a high scarcity value...
and how to set the exchange rate.
I've studied a bit more on economics
than the others.
I believe I have a better chance...
of understanding the economic designs.
All groups have an advantage
in different resources.
All three resources are needed.
The key point is to maintain
our team's advantage...
while sneaking in
the resources of the other teams.
It felt like it was going to be
a headache to go against each other.
We were all split into teams.
"You only have this. You only have that."
"You must compete against each other."
As it was designed this way,
I thought that things could get
quite cruel from the start.
We are about to enter a gruesome fight.
We have credits,
but we need lives and diamonds.
- Right.
- That must be the same for everyone.
- So...
- The ones who have a lot of diamonds...
- Right.
Don't you all need resources?
- We do.
- Could we have some time...
- to have a group meeting?
- Right. We need that.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
- Sounds good.
- Right.
I'll open the store first.
- All right.
- Let's move out...
- with our groups.
- Right.
- Gosh.
- But...
- Are we going to sit here?
- Yes.
- I'm glad I didn't become the leader.
- Great.
(Black opens the supermarket.)
(Black can track each group's
resource information in real time.)
The numbers for the first day appeared.
And there was that announcement.
"After today's announcement,"
"the total amount will not be revealed."
That got me excited.
Everyone knows the number of resources
each group has at the start,
but as time goes by,
the information asymmetry
will grow bigger.
That will make more people
need Black's help.
We can issue diamonds on the second day.
The total amount is 200.
If we issue more diamonds,
the value of the diamonds will drop...
- if the prize money doesn't get bigger.
- The value will drop.
Group White can make decisions
regarding the prize money.
This group can issue more diamonds
starting from the second day.
However, the total prize money
of 200,000 dollars will not change.
As more diamonds are issued,
the value of one diamond will drop.
For example, if there is just one diamond,
it will be worth 200,000 dollars.
But if there are two diamonds,
the value of 1 diamond
will become 100,000 dollars.
If Team White makes a deal...
to give away 100 diamonds
that are worth 100,000 dollars,
and 200 diamonds are issued the next day,
the other group's prize money
could drop to 50,000 dollars.
The number of how many we can issue
and the value drop of each diamond...
is only given to us.
The other teams don't know
that we have 8 lives and 3 credits.
- They don't.
- They might think we have none.
- Right.
It could be, "Give us 100 diamonds
for 6 lives."
It will be important
to hide this information.
If we are to survive for two days,
we need four more lives.
I think we should ask for 16 lives.
I think this is what we can say.
- "Let's all survive for four days."
- Right.
- The other groups have three members.
They need at least 12 lives.
They need 12 lives.
- To survive for four days.
- Right.
This is the total number of lives,
but they don't know how many we have.
This many are left after 24 lives.
(Remaining lives: 19)
So it won't matter if we ask for 16.
(Remaining lives: 3)
We can claim that we have fewer lives
compared to our six members.
- Shouldn't we go for that claim?
- Like that?
While keeping the line of comfort,
is this the biggest number we can ask for?
We'll say that 16 will be worth
3 days for us.
"We have six members."
"Your group can survive
for more than four days."
"We only have three days."
"Since we are at a disadvantage,"
"we should be given this much."
This is what we're aiming for.
Right.
I don't think three days' worth of lives
will be given to us.
We'll have to ask
how many they are willing to offer.
Pretend to faint
if they are willing to offer just one.
- "We're going to die."
- Well...
Well,
they could offer six lives
so we can survive for a single day.
- Right. They could do that.
- Isn't that too harsh?
Plead for their understanding.
- I will. I will, but...
- You should faint.
I want to collect
as many lives as possible.
I want to collect enough lives...
for us to survive for three days.
We were just given money.
(We were just given money.)
We might end up dying in a couple of days.
The other teams...
aren't in desperate need of money.
They will try to survive
until the very end.
That means a lot of money
will have to be used.
This was on the screen earlier.
- In our room?
- Right. In our room.
- This was on the screen.
- Right. This was on the screen.
If we have 30 lives...
Each group might have 6 lives
while Team Black has 1.
- Black has one life as well?
- Right. With that as an assumption.
Then...
he will have none after today.
- Right.
By the end of tomorrow,
he will be removed if he has no lives.
Actually,
we don't have to do anything today.
- There's nothing to worry about.
- After paying up the credits,
- we can get more tomorrow.
- Right.
- Each group...
- Why don't we give up on the prize money?
Should we send them all away
and have a good time between ourselves?
That's still a win for us.
- That's a huge win.
- Just the three of us.
Should we hang around until the end?
They're urgent right now...
- Right.
- based on this assumption.
I was so happy
that the lives were given to us.
"I won't have to worry about
survival for now."
Lives are the most crucial.
No matter how many diamonds
and credits they have,
they will all be meaningless
without any lives.
This can be used as a threat...
to drain out everything they have.
"Hand them over if you wish to live."
Our leader is a tank of ambition.
When dogs win competitions abroad,
the dogs look really proud.
She's just like a champion dog.
It's quite awkward
to compare her to a dog,
but I felt this great sense of confidence.
Things aren't bad for now.
(Team Red's Resources:
0 diamonds, 4 lives, 30 credits)
- I get the idea.
- Right.
We are the only ones...
with credits.
- Right.
Then, the lowest resource...
has the highest value.
The problem with the credits...
is that we only know
they are needed for deals.
We don't know where else they are needed.
- Right.
- The importance of credits...
is lower than lives.
Since we have 30 credits,
if a trade occurs today
and they lose their credits,
- they will have no credits tomorrow.
- Right.
- We won't be able to buy lives.
We must make a deal today to play it safe.
But the value of credits
might go up tomorrow.
How many lives shall we target?
Five.
We'll just make a big call?
We need enough to survive for three days.
- We should ask for five from Team Blue.
- Right.
I want to meet up with Black next.
I want to ask him if Team White
has the most diamonds.
And as for diamonds,
- we'll go for the minimum.
- We need them.
We can ask for 20 diamonds for 2 credits.
I don't want to give away
too many credits.
- Right.
(Maillard wants to raise the value
by limiting the distribution.)
- Yes?
- Do you have some time?
Yes. Give me a moment.
- Come to us if you have time.
- Right.
- We can give up on the diamonds.
(Team Red and Team Black meet up.)
- Right now...
- I was working on the stock.
- Oh, right. You must feel lonely.
- Right now,
- according to the rules,
- Yes?
you can't make a deal
with lives or credits.
I can't. I'm someone
who doesn't need the credits.
What I could gain from Team Red is...
- Diamonds?
- something else using the credits.
Are diamonds what you want the most
during the remaining time?
Yes, the diamonds. The prize.
- Right, the prize. I get it.
- Yes.
From what I see,
credits are important in the early stage.
- Totally.
- Since you have the upper hand,
getting as many diamonds as possible
early on seems like a good idea.
- I'll be frank with you.
- Okay.
I have zero diamonds.
- The other team has it all.
- Right.
Get as many diamonds as possible
from Team White.
When tomorrow and the day after come...
Become the best customers?
Yes, it'd be best if you do.
I wanted to seem like
a very transparent person,
and I was actually being transparent.
Using the power of the information I have,
I thought I'd be able to control them
from a favorable position.
Black has a personal goal,
and to achieve it, he must think that
it's in his best interest...
to build as much goodwill as possible.
After being nice to us,
I'm sure he'd want to stab us in the back.
But whose back will he stab?
Everyone's or a team's?
Here's a tip.
Use the lives to threaten others.
- I had the same idea.
- Right?
The value of life
will be the highest today.
You don't have any diamonds
at the moment, right?
- Right.
- I recommend securing...
as many diamonds as possible...
when there's an information gap.
I don't think it's wise to buy
many diamonds right now.
Earlier, Black said buying more
would be beneficial.
- It's currently 1,000 dollars.
- Right.
- But once more are produced,
- It could drop to 500 dollars.
say 500 diamonds,
- it'll plunge to 400 dollars per diamond.
- Right.
- The value will drop by more than half.
- True.
But if submitting one life per day
is a fixed requirement,
then the value of both lives and credits
will remain stable...
- because funds are constantly spent.
- Right.
Black is here.
- Give him a round of applause first.
- Welcome.
(Team White and Team Black
meet face to face.)
- Hi.
- Take a seat, Black.
What's going on right now?
I'm sharing my thoughts objectively today,
- without any personal interests involved.
- I see.
Nobody shared how much money they had,
but I expressed that
lives would be crucial early on,
while diamonds would matter more
in the second half.
The prices can be manipulated as desired.
Say that it was 200 today
but that becomes 2,000.
The price would suddenly drop
from 1,000 dollars to 100 dollars.
- Right.
- But they wouldn't know that.
Even if you must use many diamonds,
I think it's best to secure
many lives and credits.
But the other teams
would try to sell the least...
at a high price.
Here's what I can offer
to support Team White.
For example, I could suddenly raise
the prices tomorrow.
I can make it so that
no one except Team White can eat.
I bet they'd just starve.
Will they?
- Won't they?
- You see,
we're kind people.
- What?
- That's true.
- Do you know why we're Team White?
- We're Team White because...
we want everyone to survive...
- and strive together.
- If I'm being honest,
the more people survive,
- the more we can produce,
- True.
and that means I can mine more diamonds.
My sole aim is the diamonds.
When you've earned plenty,
you don't have to open the shop.
- Will he leave us to starve?
- The thing is,
even if I think I've earned enough,
- We could do something about it.
- Team White might suddenly print money.
That's why I must get on your good side.
True, and we must get on yours.
Exactly.
I'd appreciate it if you adored me.
- Please.
- And you're all alone.
You're adorable.
My only aim is the diamonds.
- White is the only team...
- I see.
I can coexist with.
"What is he trying to do?"
"And right there at that."
He's not taking part in the trade.
In short, he's an outsider.
He'll definitely make moves
according to rules different from ours.
That left me with no choice
but to keep my eyes on him.
He put everything into nice words,
explained the game like a game master,
and even said,
"I'm also after a particular benefit."
But how deep his evil side really goes
is something worth keeping an eye on.
Based on my experience
with survival shows,
I've learned that someone
who is kind to everyone...
is someone you should be cautious about.
One hour has passed
in the trading session.
Groups wishing to make a trade...
must have their leader bring
the necessary resources...
to the Community Center.
Team Blue, are you free?
- Yes.
- Good.
- We were about to...
- Let's have an in-depth conversation.
- Sure.
- From what I see,
the diamonds don't hold the power of life.
- That's true.
- Team Blue is who holds that power.
But our team holds the right to trade.
One of the rules was to come
to an agreement and submit one credit.
Those who want to trade decide...
- which team will submit the one credit.
- Right.
When making the trade,
our team will submit the credit.
- Okay.
- We'll give you nine credits.
Please give us 12 lives in return.
- Sorry?
- Twelve lives.
With nine credits?
The ratio is based on all the resources
currently disclosed so far.
- Our team needs credit to do anything.
- Right.
But we don't want to secure credits
by going that far.
- Really?
- Based on what you said earlier,
we can offer six lives.
And how many credits in return?
The same amount mentioned before.
You're ripping us off.
Say that...
- it's one credit per team.
- Okay.
The value of one credit
might not be the same...
as one life.
- Of one credit?
- Yes.
- I see.
- That team calculated it as...
a percentage of the total amount.
Each team needs three lives a day
to survive.
But 1 credit is needed
for a 1-time trade...
involving six people.
So, for example, that means
1 credit is worth 1-6th of a life.
But the amount used per day...
is clearly different, no?
- Life...
- Three lives are used for sure.
- But not credits.
- Three lives are used every day,
but more credits could be used than that.
- Yes.
- True, but that's currently unclear.
Since we're not sure about anything,
how about we trade tomorrow
after we find out more?
- Tomorrow?
- Yes.
You're talking about
10 credits for 6 lives.
Correct.
It feels wrong.
- I agree.
- We believe credits...
- have more value than that.
- Or...
How about 9 credits for 6 lives?
- Instead, we'll submit the one credit.
- Well...
The offer we can make is
for our team to submit the one credit...
and trade 5 credits for 6 lives.
- The same amount?
- Yes.
- We'd be trading six each in total.
If you can't agree to that,
we first want to see
how valuable credit is.
- You want to check first?
- Credits are the least abundant...
among the resources.
- Trading six each...
- Yes?
Let us discuss whether
we're willing to make such a trade...
- with the credits.
- Okay.
- That's the final offer we can make.
- Got it.
The rate of consumption may be different
from the rate for life,
but things felt off
when she wanted to trade...
six lives for ten credits.
I thought,
"We shouldn't back down anymore."
"If we accept such an offer,"
"everything might end up going the way
Team Blue wants."
I no longer wanted to make the trade.
Among the members of Team Red,
it's hard to tell
what Maillard is thinking.
He's not giving off a nice vibe, you know?
We might have a little trouble with him.
- I think doing a trade...
- About six?
- isn't that bad an idea.
- Six seems fine.
- It's just that...
- Yes?
my mean side won't die down.
I can't stand people
who hold our lifeline hostage...
and try to control it.
If only I could be like,
"Let's go down together."
- But I should calm down.
- For now.
Even if the trade falls through,
we could still survive tomorrow for now.
The value of credits might go up tomorrow.
Maillard said it with much confidence,
which we all agreed on.
You two give me reassurance.
- What?
- You know.
- If...
- Yes?
If our team only had three people like me,
I don't think we could've pulled off
a deal this bold.
I couldn't even have made such an offer.
- Hi.
- Yes, hi.
- Did you have a good chat with Team Blue?
- Yes.
- Trade...
- We're still talking.
More so because they have the lifeline.
- True, and it's important.
- It's far from easy.
You have it tough.
(Breathing in)
Why aren't you looking at us?
- We're a little weird about rich people.
- Is that so?
What's the use of being rich?
- Sorry?
- We're jealous of you,
who have many chances.
Our team just came back from
being bullied about having chances.
They said the chances weren't necessary.
- We think there's value in chances.
- Then...
How's the value of credits?
We want to secure many credits.
May we ask how much
you're willing to trade?
Honestly,
if we give you a bunch right now,
we can't help but wonder...
if the value of the diamonds we receive
will be the same tomorrow.
- The problem lies with trust.
- Correct.
We did some thinking.
Why are we Team White?
We realized money isn't something
we're that savvy with.
We're innocent and pure.
Really, this isn't all just nice words.
We were saying to each other,
"Now I see why we're Team White."
Everyone on our team is
just so kind-hearted.
- Is that so?
- So...
- "Isn't it best to survive together?"
- Nice.
If we could make a good deal
from the start,
there would be no reason for us
to devalue the currency.
Say that we release a lot of credits.
Would you be willing to keep trading...
- at the same rate later on?
- Of course.
That includes a guarantee
that we won't devalue the currency,
as well as compensation for the favor
you're doing us by making...
a generous trade in the first place.
To be frank,
we wanted to ask for 30 diamonds
for 2 credits.
- What?
- Two credits...
Our team won't gain anything
by trading diamonds.
If that's the case,
we'll need at least six credits.
- So we'd have to give you 90 diamonds.
- Yes.
- Then...
- There's no other option.
- What matters right now is lives.
- Correct.
The resources we have right now...
You won't have anything to trade for life.
- No.
- Right?
Exactly.
Then...
How far are we willing to go
with Team White's rate?
- One to ten? We went with one to fifteen.
- One to ten? One to fifteen?
- One to fifteen?
- Sixty diamonds?
Sixty is...
Did you come to an agreement?
We can offer 6 credits for 60 diamonds.
That's a little more expensive
than we imagined.
From our perspective,
we have to pay both sides
to make these purchases,
and at this point, we believe lives...
are more valuable than credits.
How does 50 diamonds sound?
- Credits are...
- Okay. We're fine with 50.
- Nice. Thank you.
- Good.
- Thank you for the easy deal!
- No problem.
We'll see you at the Community Center.
Let's go with that
since we're all in a pinch.
- Thank you very much.
- Great.
They made the deal really easy.
We planned to do a little negotiating,
but he was like, "Okay."
When Team White mentioned
wanting to keep a good relationship...
by making a good trade,
being stubborn about
our trading conditions...
didn't look all that beneficial.
Loosening up a bit
seemed like a good idea.
Shall we get straight to the point?
- Yes, let's do that.
- Good.
- We need lives, as you already know.
- Of course.
We have a big team,
so we need a handful of lives.
- How much can you offer?
- Right. You see...
We thought nine was the maximum,
but those nine aren't all for Team White.
Limiting it to nine...
It's three days' worth of lives for us.
Three days' worth? Won't you survive
even without the nine lives?
If you do the math,
it won't last us until the end.
I'm a little confused about the diamonds.
They said additional diamonds...
- will be issued starting Day Two.
- That's right.
- So the value of one diamond now...
- It'll be different.
The bottom line here
is that there's no point...
in us setting the unit price
or the quality ourselves.
- That's right.
- How many are you going to give us?
We originally planned
on giving out nine...
and were discussing how
to allocate them into a 6-3 split.
Whether we're willing
to give out more than nine is...
something I'll talk it over
with these two and see.
Right.
Team Blue appeared...
unwilling to give up any lives.
Based on our calculations,
it seemed like they had plenty
of lives to last for several days.
But they took a very defensive stance.
They won't give it to us so easily.
It's unsettling.
But if they insist
on not giving any lives,
we'll do the same and call it off.
They'll starve,
and they'll change their minds.
Either way,
they've already got it in their heads...
- that we're going to issue them anyway.
- Right.
- As much as possible...
- That's their assumption.
- That's right.
- What if they give us all the lives,
- but not much gets issued?
- Right.
Will they still be willing
to take that risk?
That still leaves us with enough
to survive for seven days.
And since we're more efficient
at generating lives...
Are you saying we should...
- give out more lives?
- Not so many.
This whole situation is too abstract.
I'm fine with whatever
the two of you decide.
We can agree
on the overall direction first,
then we can decide
the numbers accordingly.
Even during the negotiations,
I felt that the two had different goals...
and were somewhat at odds with each other.
I said earlier
that we should give Team White six...
because I didn't want
to make enemies from the start.
It doesn't have to be a beautiful picture.
If we're just looking at the value
of the goods,
Genie's calculation would make more sense.
It would be more favorable to our side.
But the goodwill we gain
by doing things differently...
is also a really important part
of the value of the exchange for me.
I can't guarantee it,
but we don't know how it'll be used.
Actually, I wouldn't say Salt
is completely passive.
She seemed like someone
who has very strong opinions of her own.
The vibe she gave off
kind of reminded me of Polar Bear.
They're the kind of people
with strong convictions.
What they want...
is ten for each life.
I think it's not bad.
It's 1 for 10,
- and they'll use the one credit.
- Okay.
All right.
- Toward coexisting.
- You can go and make the deal.
I'll go and talk to Team Red.
I'm practically running around...
like a real estate agent.
In a way, I think I've earned
everyone's trust.
Two hours have passed
in the trading session.
I'll head to the dormitory for a bit.
I really want to use
the credits to make threats.
I don't want to give out any today.
- But if we fail,
- Yes.
- only one person will be left here.
- Right.
We have to earn some lives.
- Tomorrow has to come for us to...
- Right.
have an idea about the values.
- Tomorrow is going to be hectic.
- Yes.
Tomorrow, we might regret
what we did today.
I think we'll be able
to earn something anyway.
And they'll also be able
to earn credits anyway.
That's also why
we shouldn't give out lives so easily.
That's right.
Goodness.
- We should take them all, right?
- Yes.
These are the lives.
These are worth 200,000 dollars.
It'll be over
if we just go home with these.
I have to give out 12.
Are we sure about giving out 12?
What do you think?
Let's settle on it.
Let's go with 12.
That way, we can earn things...
and still do something.
We've secured our survival
for six days anyway.
That alone can make us drop our worries.
Are we going to the Community Center?
Or do we go to the place we were earlier?
Team Blue is being way too conservative.
First,
we don't know how much
we're capable of producing.
That worries me the most.
What if we all turn out to be idiots...
and keep losing in all the games?
First of all,
I'm really...
not an intellectual person. So...
Are we sure we can sell these?
- We have to think about that.
- I'm serious.
I'm saying maybe it'd be better...
to send out less and prioritize stability.
I don't think three lives
would make so much of a difference.
There are 30 minutes remaining
before the Trading Station closes.
- So...
- Gosh.
Is Team Blue talking to Team Red?
- No.
- Team Red is over there.
- Where is Team Blue?
- Team Blue isn't around.
They haven't come yet.
There's not much time left.
- Did they disappear on us?
- I know, right?
Like this?
Let's settle this here.
We're a team.
The moment we start blaming
each other for mistakes,
- the team will fall apart.
- That's right.
That's right. For example,
the game didn't end well...
after everything,
and one of us was the reason.
Still, we earned two lives.
What do we do in that context?
- Why is Team Blue...
- Team Blue isn't coming.
Team Blue!
- What are they talking about?
- They must be discussing things...
Isn't there a time limit?
- We have 30 minutes left.
- We have less than 30 minutes left.
- Shall we proceed first?
- Should we just go ahead?
We've decided on what to do.
Are they trying to drag this out...
- No way.
- to change the exchange rate?
They wouldn't do that
starting from the first day.
I don't think they would.
But do they have more things
to talk about?
Twelve lives...
is quite a lot.
- It's not something we can ignore.
- It's worth four days for us.
But shouldn't we invest something
to earn something?
Shall we trade with Team Red first?
Let's proceed.
(Trade between Team White and Team Red:
50 diamonds with 5 credits)
(Community Center)
(Team Red pays the one credit.)
The Trading Station has been activated.
White and red.
- It was 5 to 50, right?
- Yes.
Do I just put them here?
(Exclaiming)
- This is interesting.
- Awesome.
(Depositing 50 diamonds)
(Depositing 5 credits)
We have to put them all in.
It'll take some time
because I have to deposit 50 of them.
Okay. Take your time.
I'm done.
We're checking the submitted amount.
Please wait a moment.
The trade has been completed.
Please collect your items and exit.
- Thank you. Great work.
- Thank you!
Let's keep making...
good trades together.
(Team White and Team Red's trade
has been completed.)
We don't have time.
If there are no objections, let's go.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
Six each?
(They decided to distribute 12 lives.)
Let's go.
They're coming. That's a relief.
We met earlier,
and the rest went to trade.
- We've been waiting right in front.
- Okay.
What if the numbers change later?
- I know, right?
- "One diamond has been deposited."
What is this?
- Shall we go and trade, Team White?
- Okay!
How many did you trade with that team?
- Is it a secret?
- Yes. I have to keep it like that.
We can deposit the credit here.
- We agreed that we'd pay.
- Yes.
(Team White pays the one credit.)
- The Trading Station has been activated.
- Thank you.
- They're six, right?
- Yes.
(Submitting 6 lives,
submitting 60 diamonds)
Even if I lie and say I only put one life,
- it can be checked right away.
- That's when things turn bloody.
- You can push the person right here.
- That's why it's there.
For us to fight right here.
The trade has been completed.
I feel rich.
- You have such a big team.
- Right.
We should really put all our efforts
into producing.
We'd earn enough to get by day to day.
That's why we have many members.
That's right.
What they want in the end...
is to do a 1-to-1 after taxes.
I asked if five would be okay,
and they said it was.
Is life worth that much?
Actually, 5 or 6
doesn't make much of a difference.
Let's use one less card.
We can profit from this.
- Okay.
We were nervous right until we came out,
and we kept talking about whether
we should give out a little less.
(Trade between Team Red and Team Blue:
5 credits with 5 lives)
(Team Red pays the one credit.)
The Trading Station has been activated.
- It's 5 with 5, right?
- Yes.
(Submitting 5 lives, submitting 5 credits)
We're checking the submitted amount.
Please wait a moment.
The trade has been completed.
- They're coming.
Did you succeed in making a deal?
We made a smooth deal.
(All trading for Day 1 has ended.)
- Yes!
At first, we kept having...
conflicts around the number of lives.
But I was worried
people might want to get rid of me...
if I acted too greedily
from the first day.
So I tried to be nice,
but I'm not sure.
Was I nice?
No one knows the value of the credits yet.
So I feel like if we'd been
a little bolder,
we might have hit it big tomorrow.
But I think securing
the minimum level of lives...
was a necessary thing to do.
We may have been a bit generous today,
but I think we need to be a little firm.
Either way, the currency will be issued.
So we're planning...
to make it clear
that we have more leverage...
than they think.
Should we leave them in our dormitories?
Does anyone smoke?
- I smoke.
- That's a relief.
They have a connection now.
- Smoking connection.
- Yes.
- So this is the hub.
- I guess we can talk here.
- That's right.
It's peaceful now.
It's peaceful on the first day.
Starting from the second day...
(Sighing)
It's going to get crazy from tomorrow.
- There'll be cracks from tomorrow.
- Right.
I'm a bit scared.
Since we have many members,
some of us are bound to be eliminated.
Right.
Only Vector and I were smokers.
I was surprised that no one else smoked.
I'm actually worried...
that people might think...
we're plotting something together.
On the other hand, I think I could get
information from Black...
and communicate with him.
- Are you done?
- Yes. Shall we leave?
- I'll smoke a little longer.
- Okay.
- You're smoking two in a row.
- Yes.
- I couldn't smoke earlier.
- Right.
I actually don't smoke,
but I forced myself to practice smoking.
I got there,
and there was only one smoker.
In that case,
it's more important to talk
to the other 11 people.
But it'd be weird to suddenly say...
that I quit smoking
after smoking on the first day.
So I'm in a very weird situation.
I wish someone would just carry me.
I know, right? It's too high up.
(Team Red and Team Blue
are climbing up to their dormitories.)
- This is exercise.
- It's a good workout.
This isn't fair for those
who don't exercise.
Team White's dormitory is really big.
But to go there...
I know, right? It's too far.
That's really tough.
- That would be a real workout.
- Right.
(Exclaiming)
- I'm tired.
- Seriously.
You did so well today.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- I could trust you.
You were also good at playing
a little hard to get in negotiations.
- We're here.
- Goodness.
Our important lives.
Please.
(Team White's Resources:
90 diamonds, 14 lives, 7 credits)
Don't let the values drop.
(Team White's Resources:
90 diamonds, 14 lives, 7 credits)
- How many do we have? Sixty?
- We have sixty diamonds.
I wonder if they traded 1-to-1 too.
I hope we didn't make a losing deal.
I don't think we did.
The current price is...
They said it was 1,000 dollars each.
That's 60,000 dollars.
- That's a lot.
- It's 60,000 dollars.
I feel satisfied with 50 diamonds.
(Team Red's Resources:
50 diamonds, 9 lives, 18 credits)
It's dinner time.
All residents, please gather
at the Town Hall for dinner.
(Team Black's supermarket is open!)
So this is how it looks.
There's a storage place.
There's jjajang...
and yukgaejang.
- Ramyeon!
- There's ramyeon!
- Who wants ramyeon?
- Pick what you want.
- There's a variety.
- We have many cup ramyeons.
That's very...
You look very rich.
Ramyeon.
- That's so cool.
- I'm so jealous.
- So cool. Right.
- You look like someone with power.
- He looks wealthy.
- That's right.
Eight boxed meals...
and four fried chickens?
A special meal has been ordered.
It's on its way,
- A special meal?
- so please wait a moment.
- A special meal is on its way.
- It's on me today.
The boss.
They're giving us fried chicken
from Day One.
You have to try it to keep wanting it.
Right.
(After fried chicken,
then comes the pork belly.)
It's pork belly!
Help us with the meat, Maillard.
The grilling expert is here.
That's Maillard.
The Maillard master.
He's really living up to his name.
I'm really curious to see
what Maillard's meat tastes like.
It's just grilling them in a frying pan.
Can't everyone in Korea cook this?
The oil...
There's pizza here.
That looks good. It looks really good.
There's a real expert vibe.
It looks good.
- Thank you.
Well done.
- Well done.
- Take a seat.
Shall we clink with the pork belly?
- Okay!
- Dumplings and pork belly clink.
All right.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Cheers.
The pork belly tastes great.
There's mustard in the pizza?
(Exclaiming)
This is good.
- He grilled it so well.
- You're really good with meat.
Thank you.
Have some soju as well.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, boss.
- I'll just drink a little.
- Sure.
- Since it's the first day.
- Yes.
There.
- Do you drink?
- Yes.
I'm not sure if this is correct...
(Exclaiming)
Will you start business
starting lunch tomorrow?
That's right.
What about breakfast?
You have to take some for breakfast today.
- Yes.
- Let's pack some food.
- Eggs.
- Things like eggs.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll have to pay for them.
Right.
I think all the food
is going to become really valuable.
We could roughly estimate
how many we all had today,
but starting tomorrow,
- we won't have any idea.
- We wouldn't know.
It's really hard to put a value on things.
Only Vector knows.
I'm the only one
who knows the golden ratio.
- I envy you.
- Right.
But it's useless for me.
I have to keep the balance.
I'll provide everyone
the same information fairly.
Since I'm alone, I'll probably
get to do something else separately.
Then the supermarket owner
will just keep earning money?
- That's weird?
- Isn't that weird?
- It's weird.
- It's too good.
- Right.
- It's just so good.
There's no way something like that exists.
Vector is under a lot of suspicion.
His play style is too nice.
People who carry this kind of kindness
into a survival game...
have a slightly different mission.
So far, Vector has no risks.
He can just eat whatever he wants,
and when people come,
he can get diamonds
to earn the prize money.
If that's how it will end,
it wouldn't make any sense.
Maybe because it's the first day,
he let the child taste the candy.
"Isn't it tasty?"
He lets us eat so much...
and tells us to pay from the next day.
Maybe he was just laying the groundwork.
He's just training us
like we're a bunch of puppies.
Puppies are trained using food.
He fed us tasty meat.
He's going to tighten the leash now.
When trades don't work out,
Yes?
could things come to blows?
A real-life fight?
- A fight...
- A real-life fight?
- A real-life fight.
- There's a chance of a real-life fight.
Desperation could lead to that.
If we get desperate...
You were cooler than we thought.
You could have held out
a little longer, right, Team Blue?
You could have said,
- "Try holding out until tomorrow."
- We could have done that.
- We could've said, "Take it or leave it."
- Yes.
We could just choose not to give them out.
We could just let everyone get eliminated.
That's what we said at first
in a joking manner,
but we wanted it to go
peacefully on Day One.
Don't say such harsh words.
Right. We wanted to survive together
for a long time.
Yes. We also gave you some things.
It'd be really sad
when people disappear...
when we've been bustling around like this.
- That's right.
- Right.
These people will be gone by tomorrow.
You've got to play the game
for what it is.
How could you call this a game?
This was your plan all along!
Your excuse is so lame.
(Life submission)
Something's playing.
I'd like to announce
today's final official event.
Life submissions will take place...
- over the next hour.
- Life submission.
- Life submission?
- See you later.
- This is scary.
Each group's leader is asked
to prepare enough lives...
for the number of people in their team...
and submit them to the Community Center.
Any resident whose life...
has not been submitted on their behalf
within the allotted time...
will be immediately removed
from the premises.
The six of us are one.
We could submit one life.
We're one?
- We're one.
- I agree.
- That's a good idea.
- Nice.
- Right?
- That's right.
- We're one.
- Of course.
- I'll go and submit our precious lives.
- Okay.
- I'll go with her.
Let's go.
See you.
The leader has to do...
- many bothersome things.
- Right.
It'd be tiresome.
- Three.
- Thank you for doing that.
It's all right.
I'll go and submit these.
- On their behalf...
- Why are they giving us an hour?
We might have to fight over this later.
For example, if we have two left,
we have to decide...
- who will be eliminated.
- You...
You could take these three...
If you decide not to keep us alive
and submit only one...
If I submit only one,
the two of you will die?
This is a bit...
- Is that what it is?
- Well...
- Should I come with you?
- No.
We trust you.
You won't be able to play the games alone.
- We can pack our bags.
- It'll be tough.
If I only submit mine,
I'd be killing the rest of my team.
If there's only one person,
they won't need any lives.
- If the leader...
- Yes?
- submits only one life,
- Yes.
the other two will die, right?
They said we wouldn't need lives
if only one team member was left.
Gosh! That's true.
I suddenly felt more powerful.
The leader can decide
whether or not to keep someone alive...
during the submission.
Being a leader...
is quite important.
(Life Submission for Day 1)
(Donkey, Maillard, Izaha)
Please check the contents
of the central box...
and assign lives
to the residents of your choice.
(Life Submission for Day 1)
If I only submit mine,
I'd be killing the rest of my team.
(Maillard)
If there's only one person,
they won't need any lives.
(Life Submission for Day 1)
(Maillard)
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)